Button, Daniel Evan; Papers apap231
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- HR, Legislation and Bills, 1964-1971; Undated; 1; 4.8 cubic ft.
  - H.R. 13832 to prescribe mininum standards for railroad passenger service, 1969 (Box 3 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 93)
  - H.R. 13870 urban property protection and insurance amendments of 1969 (Box 3 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 94)
  - H.R. 13913 to amend the Land and Water Conservation Fund Act of 1965, 1970 (Box 3 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 95)
  - H.R. 13929 unsolicited mailing of polarity offensive material, 1969 (Box 3 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 96)
  - H.R. 13950 Federal Coal Mine Health and Safety Act of 1969 [roll call 248] (Box 3 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 97)
  - H.R. 13953 to require the secretary of labor to collect dissminate employment information regarding local law enforcement agencies, 1969 (Box 3 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 98)
  - H.R. 13958 Federal Health and Safety Act of 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 1)
  - H.R. 13973 unsolicited and potentially offensive sexual materials, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 2)
  - H.R. 13987 to provide for the licensing of personnel on certain vessels, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 3)
  - H.R. 14011 to provide for the establishment of a commission marihuana, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 4)
  - H.R. 174030 to extend the authority to transfer peanut average allotment, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 5)
  - H.R. 14064 to establish a grant in aid program to encourage licensing by the states of motor vevicle mechanics, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 6)
  - H.R. 14127 joint commission on coinage, Button did not vote [roll call 101, 131, 169, 228], 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 7)
  - H.R. 14148 to provide increases in benefits under the old age survivors and disability insurance program, 1969; Undated (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 8)
  - H.R. 14159 making appropriations for public works, water pollution control [roll call 210], 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 9)
  - H.R. 14237 to amend The Mental Retardation Facilities and Community Mental Centers Constitution Act of 1963, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 10)
  - H.R. 14261 to make grants to conduct special education programs and activities concerning the use of drugs, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 11)
  - H.R. 14377 to amend the social security act concerning psychiatric benefits, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 12)
  - H.R. 14431 to provide increase in benefits under the old age, survivors, and disability insurance program, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 13)
  - H.R. 14465 airport and airway user charges [roll call 264], 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 14)
  - H.R. 14490 to authorize the disposal of nickel from national stockpile, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 15)
  - H.R. 14580 foreign aid authorization [roll calls 284, 285, 286], 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 16)
  - H.R. 14519 to establish an Office of Consumer Affairs, 1969; Undated (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 17)
  - H.R. 14646 Connecticut-New York Transportation Compact [roll call 324], 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 18)
  - H.R. 14705 unemployment compensation [passed roll call 231-232], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 19)
  - H.R. 14716 National Drug Testing and Education Act of 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 20)
  - H.R. 14751 military construction [roll call 270, 271], 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 21)
  - H.R. 14794 Department of Transportation appropriations bill [roll call 277], 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 22)
  - H.R. 14913 to amend Title II of the Social Security Act, 1969; Undated (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 23)
  - H.R. 14965 the Uniform Comprehensive Assistance and Land Acquisition Act, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 24)
  - H.R. 15073 to amend Deposit Insurance Act [passed roll call 140], 1969-1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 25)
  - H.R. 15090 Department of Defense appropriation bill [roll call 306], 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 26)
  - H.R. 15095 Social Security amendments of 1969 [roll call 323] (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 27)
  - H.R. 15124 establish an istitute for continuing studies of juvonile justice, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 28)
  - H.R. 15143 to provide the grade of Lieutenant General [passed roll call 48], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 29)
  - H.R. 15149 foreign aid appropriations [roll call 309], 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 30)
  - H.R. 15348 to amend the E.P.D, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 31)
  - H.R. 15361 youth conservation corps [passed roll call 169], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 32)
  - H.R. 15377 to establish a national program to provide income supplements, 1969 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 33)
  - H.R. 15424 to amend the Merchant Marine Act of 1936, [passed roll call 137], 1970; Undated (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 34)
  - H.R. 15628 Foreign Military Sales Act [defeated roll call 207-208], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 35)
  - H.R. 15693 protestion of minors from receipt of obscene material through mail, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 36)
  - H.R. 15694 Coast Guard authorization, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 37)
  - H.R. 15712 amend public works and economic development, 1970-1971 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 38)
  - H.R. 15728 to authorize the extension of certain naval vessel loans, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 39)
  - H.R. 15777 School Construction Act of 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 40)
  - H.R. 15828 diposition waste materials in the New York Bight, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 41)
  - H.R. 15852 to improve the judicial machinery of military court-martial, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 42)
  - H.R. 15860 the Scrap Auto Act, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 43)
  - H.R. 15931 Labor H.E.W. [roll call 25, 26, 27], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 44)
  - H.R. 15959 prevent pollution by imposing a tax on soft drinks, beer and alcohol containers, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 45)
  - H.R. 16039 recycling materials from solid waste, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 46)
  - H.R. 16062 to amend the Wagner O'Day Act, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 47)
  - H.R. 16065 to amend the National Foundation on the Arts and the Humanities Act of 1965 [passed roll call 197], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 48)
  - H.R. 16067 to make armed robbery of gasoline stations federal offense, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 49)
  - Environment HRs 16223, 15289, 16039 and H.J.R 54, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 50)
  - H.R. 16223 fish and wildlife service involving pesticides, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 51)
  - H.R. 16265 Comprehensive Child Development Act of 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 52)
  - H.R. 16311 family assistance plan [passed roll calls 72, 82, 83], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 53)
  - H.R. 16328 Newsmen's Privilege Act, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 54)
  - H.R. 16345 patent regulations, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 55)
  - H.R. 16366 payments in lieu of property taxes, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 56)
  - H.R. 16376 improving police services, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 57)
  - H.R. 16414 Pollution Abatement Act of 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 58)
  - H.R. 16476 to make it lawful to fly kites in D.C. [passed non record vote], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 59)
  - H.R. 16520 noise control, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 60)
  - H.R. 16542 to amend title 39 United States code to regulate the mailing of unsolicited credit cards, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 61)
  - H.R. 16595 to authorize appropriations for activities of the National Science Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 62)
  - H.R. 16601 National Guard, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 63)
  - H.R. 16686 gold medal for Martin Luther King Junior's widow, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 64)
  - H.R. 16688 federal civilian employment, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 65)
  - H.R. 16713 motor vehicle emission standards, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 66)
  - H.R. 16785 Occupational Safety and Health Act, 1970; Undated (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 67)
  - H.R. 16900 treasury post office appropriations [passed roll call 73], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 68)
  - H.R. 16916 office of education appropriations bill [passed voice vote], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 69)
  - H.R. 16968 adjustment of government contribution for federal employment health benefits [passed roll call 219], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 70)
  - H.R. 17005 to amend the fair packaging and leveling act, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 71)
  - H.R. 17032 unmarried individuals and income splitting benefits, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 72)
  - H.R. 17070 postal reform [passed roll call 171, 179, 180], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 73)
  - H.R. 17108 the Narcotics Education Act of 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 74)
  - H.R. 17123 military procurement research and development [roll call 103, 104], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 75)
  - H.R. 17138 DC police firemen and teachers salary increase act [passed roll call 110], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 76)
  - H.R. 17192 orderly trade in textiles and leather, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 77)
  - H.R. 17247 "Robert Francis Kennedy Federal Office Building", 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 78)
  - H.R. 17255 Clean Air Act Amendments of 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 79)
  - H.R. 17277 Native American federal benefits, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 80)
  - H.R. 17362 prohibit unsilicited distribution of credit cards, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 81)
  - H.R. 17399 supplemental appropriations [passed roll call 107, 108], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 82)
  - H.R. 17405 Atomic Energy Commission authorization, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 83)
  - H.R. 17495 Emergency Home Finance Act of 1970 [passed roll call 190, 191] (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 84)
  - H.R. 17550 Social Security amendments [passed call roll 132, 133, 135, 136], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 85)
  - H.R. 17570 heart disease cancer stroke and kidney disease amendments [passed roll call 276], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 86)
  - H.R. 17601 to exempt FHA and Veterans Administration mortages and loans [defeated roll call 139], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 87)
  - H.R. 17604 military construction authorization [passed roll call 130-131], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 88)
  - H.R. 17697 hurricane protection, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 89)
  - H.R. 17698 standards for training National Guard, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 90)
  - H.R. 17711 to amend D.C. Cooperative Association Act [passed non record vote], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 91)
  - H.R. 17731 to attend the Federal Aviation Act of 1958, 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 92)
  - H.R. 17735 firearms control, Undated (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 93)
  - H.R. 17755 making appropriations for Department of Transportation [passed of voice vote, previous roll call 146], 1970 (Box 4 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 94)
  - H.R. 17802 to increase the public debt limit [passed roll call 82, 83], 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 1)
  - H.R. 17809 prevailiing rate pay system for government employees [pass roll call 283], 1970; Undated (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 2)
  - H.R. 17867 foreign aid appropriations [passed roll call 132], 1970; Undated (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 3)
  - H.R. 17923 Department of Agriculture appropriation bill [passed voice vote], 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 4)
  - H.R. 17977 limit the distribution of mailing lists by federal agencies, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 5)
  - H.R. 17990 military construction appropriation bill [passed roll call 167], 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 6)
  - H.R. 18006 judicial proceedings penalty, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 7)
  - H.R. 18025 to create a new voluntary civilian service as an alternative to military service, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 8)
  - Legis, H.R. 18288 Kupferman, tax credit for education expenses [2389 and 5398], 1966-1967 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 9)
  - H.R. 18312 airline tax, 1970; Undated (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 10)
  - H.R. 18403 federal pay camparibility system, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 11)
  - H.R. 18434 political broadcasting amendment [passed roll call 271], 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 12)
  - H.R. 18468 to amend the Social Security concerning psychiatric benefits available under Title XVIII and XIX, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 13)
  - H.R. 18515 Labor H.E.W. appropriation bill for 1971 [passed roll call 233], 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 14)
  - H.R. 18566 to amend the tariff schedule of the U.S. with respect to the duties on stainless steel and on articles made from such sheets, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 15)
  - H.R. 18583 comprehensive Drug Abuse Prevention and Control Act, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 16)
  - H.R. 18636 provide for a recount of the population of any state or locality which believes its polution was undercounted in the 1970 census (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 17)
  - H.R. 18669 flag bill, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 18)
  - H.R. 18725 to establish a commission on the organization of the government of D.C. [passed roll call 266], 1970; Undated (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 19)
  - H.R. 18737 "Housing Rights Act of 1970" (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 20)
  - H.R. 18786 to encourage medical personnel to practice in areas where shortages of such personnel exist, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 21)
  - H.R. 18823 to establish an improved program for the benefit of producers and consumers of dairy products, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 22)
  - H.R. 18901 to establish a commission on the medical and psychological adequacy of the physical and mental examinations conducted by the armed forces with respect to registraints under selective service laws, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 23)
  - H.R. 19903 amends Title 10 of the United States code to provide that members of the armed forces be assigned to duty stations near their homes after serving in combat zones, 1970 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 24)
  - H.R. 19650 Department of Peace, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 25)
  - Stratton's Motion [roll call 211], 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 26)
  - Vietnam War Moratorium [roll call 221 and 224], 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 27)
  - Week of February 3, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 28)
  - Week of February 17, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 29)
  - Week of February 24, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 30)
  - Week of March 3, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 31)
  - Week of March 17, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 32)
  - Week of March 24, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 33)
  - Week of March 31, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 34)
  - Week of April 14, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 35)
  - Week of April 21 [includes vote], 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 36)
  - Week of April 28, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 37)
  - Week of May 5, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 38)
  - Week of May 12, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 39)
  - Week of May 19, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 40)
  - Week of May 26, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 41)
  - Week of June 2, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 42)
  - Week of June 9, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 43)
  - Week of June 16, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 44)
  - Week of June 23, 1969 (Box 5 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 45)
  - Week of June 30, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 1)
  - Week of July 7, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 2)
  - Week of July 14, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 3)
  - Week of July 21, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 4)
  - Week of July 28, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 5)
  - Week of August 4, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 6)
  - Week of August 11, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 7)
  - Week of September 1, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 8)
  - Week of September 8, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 9)
  - Week of September 15, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 10)
  - Week of September 22, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 11)
  - Week of September 29, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 12)
  - Week of October 6, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 13)
  - Week of October 13, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 14)
  - Week of October 20, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 15)
  - Week of October 27, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 16)
  - Week of November 3, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 17)
  - Week of November 10, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 18)
  - Week of November 17, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 19)
  - Week of November 24, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 20)
  - Week of December 1, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 21)
  - Week of December 8, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 22)
  - Week of December 15, 1969 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 23)
  - Week of January 19, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 24)
  - Week of January 26, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 25)
  - Week of February 2, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 26)
  - Week of February 16, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 27)
  - Week of February 23, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 28)
  - Week of March 2, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 29)
  - Week of March 9, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 30)
  - Week of March 16, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 31)
  - Week of March 23, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 32)
  - Week of April 6, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 33)
  - Week of April 13, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 34)
  - Week of April 27, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 35)
  - Week of May 4, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 36)
  - Week of May 11, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 37)
  - Week of May 18, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 38)
  - Week of May 25, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 39)
  - Week of June 1, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 40)
  - Week of June 29, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 41)
  - Week of August 3, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 42)
  - Week of June 8, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 43)
  - Week of June 13, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 44)
  - Week of June 22, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 45)
  - Week of July 6, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 46)
  - Week of July 13, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 47)
  - Week of July 20, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 48)
  - Week of July 27, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 49)
  - Week of August 6, 1970 (Box 6 (1-HR, Legislation and Bills), Folder 50)
- Subject Files, 1962-1971; Undated; 2; 4 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains material about Albany, national and world events during the late 1960s. There is notable information about Albany’s Arbor Hill neighbrohood, Schenectady plants, and General Electric. There is also material concerning Laos, Cambodia, ALCO, and AID. There are pamphlets and booklets about current events.
  Series 2 also contains information about what Button called an “unholy wedlock” between conservative Republicans and Democrats. Button stated it was the first time in New York State history that the conservative party endorsed a “slate of” Democrats in a county election.
  - Albany anti-poverty, 1970; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Albany local issues, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Albany riot, 1967 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - "Albany student conference on representatives" - Extensions of remarks, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Arbor Hill, 1967 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Babe Ruth baseball, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Background material fact sheet, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Barnett Fowler, 1967 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Better Neighborhoods Inc" - record insert, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Bipartism resolution on U.S. policy in Vietnam, 1967 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Bulgaria: Anniversary of Petkov Execution, 1968 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Button amendment, postal reform, 1970; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Campus disorders, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Captive Nations Week, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Census - [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - CIA supervision, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Cohoes model cities, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Cohoes, New York, 1967 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Committee on Post Office and Civil Service, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Committee to study Pacification Program in Vietnam, 1967 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Communist expansion and "Captive Nations", 1968-1969 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 21)